<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>HBO Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://hbo.online.mills.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://hbo.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:47:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/HBOmain.png</url>
	<title>HBO Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://hbo.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chris Hemsworth opens up about &#8216;unpredictable&#8217; Thor 5; Actor reveals conditions if he plans return to MCU</title>
		<link>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/chris-hemsworth-opens-up-about-unpredictable-thor-5-actor-reveals-conditions-if-he-plans-return-to-mcu/</link>
					<comments>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/chris-hemsworth-opens-up-about-unpredictable-thor-5-actor-reveals-conditions-if-he-plans-return-to-mcu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hbo.online.mills.edu/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Chris Hemsworth, the famous Australian actor is best known for his portrayal of the iconic character Thor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe films including the Avengers franchise. The talented actor portrayed the various shades of his celebrated character with absolute ease, thanks to his exceptional acting skills and most importantly, his unparalleled comic timing. Even...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chris Hemsworth, the famous Australian actor is best known for his portrayal of the iconic character Thor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe films including the Avengers franchise. The talented actor portrayed the various shades of his celebrated character with absolute ease, thanks to his exceptional acting skills and most importantly, his unparalleled comic timing. Even though Chris Hemsworth has been experimenting in his acting with a great variety of characters, the audiences, especially the MCU fans are eagerly waiting for him to play Thor, once again.</p>
<p>Chris Hemsworth opens up about playing Thor again<br />
In his recent interview with Entertainment Weekly, Chris Hemsworth opened up about the possibilities of playing the famous Marvel character once again, in Thor 5. For the unversed, the actor had earlier opined that Thor 4 was way too &#8216;silly&#8217;, and admitted that it disappointed the common audiences and Marvel fans, alike. So, Hemsworth is very sure that he doesn&#8217;t want to continue to play Thor in the fifth installment of the franchise if it is not &#8216;unpredictable&#8217;. He also added that he doesn&#8217;t want to risk playing the character to the extent where the Marvel fans start &#8216;rolling their eyes&#8217;.</p>
<p>&#8220;I’ve got to be careful how I word that because I have no idea what’s happening in the next phase. There are always conversations… Before anything is official, people are throwing around ideas. But officially, I don’t know,&#8221; stated the actor, who also confirmed that Thor 5 is not being &#8216;officially&#8217; planned, so far. &#8220;I don’t want to continue to do it until people are so exhausted that they roll their eyes when they see me come on the screen as that character,&#8221; added the actor.</p>
<p>&#8220;If the audience wants to see it, and if there’s something that we believe is exciting and fun, then great. I’ve loved being able to reinvent that character. But I don’t have the answer yet. I would love to try and figure out how we can do that again and keep it a little unpredictable,&#8221; concluded Chris Hemsworth.</p>
<p>Chris Hemsworth&#8217;s work front<br />
The popular star was recently seen in Extraction 2, which is a sequel to the famous Netflix film which was released in 2020. He is reprising the role of Kyle Rake, an Australian SAS operator turned black ops mercenary in the film, which premiered on June 16, 2023.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/chris-hemsworth-opens-up-about-unpredictable-thor-5-actor-reveals-conditions-if-he-plans-return-to-mcu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Flash emerges the 6th biggest Hollywood opener of 2023 in India; Netts Rs 4.15 crores on day 1</title>
		<link>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/the-flash-emerges-the-6th-biggest-hollywood-opener-of-2023-in-india-netts-rs-4-15-crores-on-day-1/</link>
					<comments>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/the-flash-emerges-the-6th-biggest-hollywood-opener-of-2023-in-india-netts-rs-4-15-crores-on-day-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hbo.online.mills.edu/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Flash starring Ezra Miller had an ordinary first day in India as it collected around Rs 4.15 crores nett on its opening day in India. It was a Thursday release so it wasn&#8217;t able to get the benefit of the current which films generally tend to get on Friday since it is preceded by...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Flash starring Ezra Miller had an ordinary first day in India as it collected around Rs 4.15 crores nett on its opening day in India. It was a Thursday release so it wasn&#8217;t able to get the benefit of the current which films generally tend to get on Friday since it is preceded by a couple of holidays. While the film was fortunate to get no competition on its first day in India, it will be competing with a juggernaut like Adipurush from its second day. In all likelihood, there may be a drop in collections on day 2 and then the film will hope to match its opening day numbers on Saturday and Sunday.</p>
<p>The Flash&#8217;s Opening In India Is Lower Than Expectations<br />
The Flash&#8217;s opening is lesser than Spider-Man: Across The Spiderverse in India and that&#8217;s slightly appalling since the Spider-Man film was animated and the animated format is not wholeheartedly supported by Indian moviegoers. It did seem like The Flash could register a greater opening than the web slinger based on the advances but that was not to be as the on-the-day movement was relatively slower. The opening of The Flash is greater than Transformers: Rise Of The Beasts but Transformers has never been that big a franchise in India and the numbers that it has gotten are higher than what the trade had expected from it. In the case of The Flash, it is the opposite as expectations pinned on The Flash were higher. Fast X retains its number one position while Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania, Guardians Of The Galaxy Volume 3 and John Wick: Chapter 4 take the second, third and fourth spot respectively when it comes to the nett opening of Hollywood films in India.</p>
<p>The Flash Has Taken A Soft Start And The Opening Weekend Seems To Be Sub-150 Million Dollars Worldwide<br />
The Flash is projected to take an opening of less than 150 million dollars worldwide. Over 50 percent of its takings, that is around 75 million dollars are expected to come from outside of USA and Canada. The domestic competition for the film is fierce with a lot of competing releases fighting for screens and audiences. The Flash will be the biggest box office earner for the week but that was never that big a deal with Transformers: Rise Of The Beasts, Spider-Man: Across The Spider-Verse and The Little Mermaid in their 2nd, 3rd and 4th week respectively. The four films alone may ensure a weekend of around or over 150 million dollars in the home market.</p>
<p>Following Are The Top Hollywood Film Openers Of 2023 In India (Nett)<br />
Fast X : Rs 12.50 crores<br />
Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania : Rs 8.50 crores<br />
Guardians Of The Galaxy: Volume 3 : Rs 6.75 crores<br />
John Wick: Chapter 4 : Rs 6.50 crores<br />
Spider-Man: Across The Spider-Verse : Rs 4.20 crores<br />
The Flash : Rs 4.15 crores<br />
Transformers: Rise Of The Beasts : Rs 4 crores</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/the-flash-emerges-the-6th-biggest-hollywood-opener-of-2023-in-india-netts-rs-4-15-crores-on-day-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adipurush Hindi Advance Bookings: Prabhas&#8217; epic sells 2.85 lakh tickets in national chains for opening day</title>
		<link>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/adipurush-hindi-advance-bookings-prabhas-epic-sells-2-85-lakh-tickets-in-national-chains-for-opening-day/</link>
					<comments>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/adipurush-hindi-advance-bookings-prabhas-epic-sells-2-85-lakh-tickets-in-national-chains-for-opening-day/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://hbo.online.mills.edu/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Prabhas led Adipurush, directed by Om Raut and co-starring Saif Ali Khan, Kriti Sanon and Sunny Singh is all set to release. The film has witnessed very good advance bookings for its Hindi version, purely based on the numbers and not the means by which a chunk of them have been ensured. The advance numbers...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prabhas led Adipurush, directed by Om Raut and co-starring Saif Ali Khan, Kriti Sanon and Sunny Singh is all set to release. The film has witnessed very good advance bookings for its Hindi version, purely based on the numbers and not the means by which a chunk of them have been ensured. The advance numbers have confirmed that Adipurush will become the second biggest opener of the year for its Hindi version, just behind Pathaan and on an all India and worldwide level, Adipurush will become the biggest opener of the year by an around 10-15 percent margin. The global first day takings at the box office shall be in the north of Rs 120 crores gross.</p>
<p>Adipurush Sells 2.85 Lakh Tickets In National Chains For The Opening Day In Hindi<br />
The 3 national chains of India, namely PVR, Inox and Cinepolis have cumulatively sold around 2.85 lakh tickets for the opening day of Adipurush (Hindi), thus helping it secure the fourth place in the list of highest advance bookings in the national chains for the opening day, in the Hindi language, post pandemic. While Pathaan sits at the top, KGF: Chapter 2 and Brahmastra settle for the second and third spot respectively. PVR is obviously the leading national movie chain, followed by Inox and then Cinepolis. Including the ticket sales of Adipurush in Telugu, the total count of tickets sold in the national chains for the opening day go up to well over 4 lakhs. If films (Hindi language) of all time are considered, the advances of Adipurush are the 12th highest.</p>
<p>Following Is The List Of Indian Films That Have Sold The Highest Number Of Tickets In National Chains (Hindi Language Only)<br />
Bahubali 2: 6.50 Lakhs<br />
Pathaan: 5.56 Lakhs<br />
KGF Chapter 2: 5.15 Lakhs<br />
War: 4.05 Lakhs<br />
Thugs Of Hindostan: 3.46 Lakhs<br />
Prem Ratan Dhan Payo: 3.40 Lakhs<br />
Bharat: 3.15 Lakhs<br />
Sultan: 3.10 Lakhs<br />
Dangal: 3.05 Lakhs<br />
Brahmastra: 3.02 Lakhs<br />
Sanju: 2.94 Lakhs<br />
Adipurush 2.85 lakhs<br />
Tiger Zinda Hai: 2.76 Lakhs<br />
Mission Mangal: 2.71 Lakhs</p>
<p>Movie Chains Like MovieMax Have Observed Very Pleasing Ticket Sales<br />
The pre-bookings for Adipurush (Hindi) are genuinely promising in a lot of small chains and centers but the conspicuous way the ticket purchases have happened across national chains have garnered more attention than they should have. To note, a non national chain like MovieMax has sold around 10,000 tickets for the opening day and 20,000 tickets for the weekend purely in Hindi. The Telugu version of the film has sold around 11,000 tickets in total, taking the cumulative weekend total to 31,000 tickets which is very good. MovieMax is not a high-end chain and focuses on middle class folks and for the film to sell these many tickets surely is encouraging.</p>
<p>Adipurush has a lot going for itself and if the content clicks with the audience that it is targetting, it can really manage to do some excellent numbers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://hbo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/16/adipurush-hindi-advance-bookings-prabhas-epic-sells-2-85-lakh-tickets-in-national-chains-for-opening-day/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
